

# Contacts Velikiy Novgorod, Russia muricorabota@yandex.ru

murikuk.com

linkedin.com/in/murad-kukuev

# Specialization

Web Design & Development
Brand Identity & Strategy
Search Engine Optimization
Web Content & Creative Writing

### Languages

Russian (Native)
English (Professional Working)
Italian (Professional Working)
German (Elementary)

## Murad Kukuev

#### General information

My profession is to create beautiful and reliable websites, and if you need a high-quality and full-fledged website - contact me. Experience 5 years - participated in the creation of a large number of sites and apps. From recent work:

https://murikuk.com/

http://rmk-group.ru/

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=sonomurad.

com

In my work I use the following tools and languages: WordPress, Modx, Figma, Photoshop, GIMP, Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, JavaScript, Python, Java...

I have experience working in a team and experience in managing people - was the head of the department of 14 employees. I appreciate responsibility and reliability in people, in work - quality.

Married, have 2 children. I like to read books, play guitar.

# Experience

"Web Design Agency Murico" - Head & Web Designer

February 2016 - Present

Velikiy Novgorod (Russia)

"Novgorod Metallurgical Plant" - Engineer for design and estimate work

April 2012 - January 2016

Velikiy Novgorod (Russia)

#### Education

Dagestan State Technical University

Master of Science - MS, Hydraulic engineer · (1992 - 1998)

Makhachkala (Russia)

High School # 13

Graduate · (1982 - 1992)

Makhachkala (USSR)